What we're going to talk about regarding self hypnosis is how do you focus on your feelings in hypnosis?
Well, one important thing to know before we actually get into that is to know that when you're in hypnosis you have the uncanny ability to feel much more deeply than you do in an awake state.
You also have the ability to see yourself where you want to be.
You have the ability to visualize and know.
Not all of us see things in hypnosis because we may not be visual people.
However, we do either feel where we want to be or we just somehow know where we want to be and some of us even hear what we want to hear.
But here we have Brad deep in hypnosis and I'm talking, I know that I'm not disturbing him because he's very practiced at being in hypnosis.
But, I'm going to ask him some questions.
I'm focusing on his feelings in hypnosis.
Now, we have already set the intention that what he wants to be is a competitive golfer, not having to compete daily since he is a business owner, but have the fun loving spirit and know that he is competing yet he is not taking golf to seriously.
That's the intention that he has set for this self hypnotic session.
So, what he wants to be focusing on is the feelings of being a very happy, joyful golfer playing at a competitive level.
So, Brad in hypnosis, I'm just going to ask you, keep focusing on that and if you can just tell us how it is that you feel.
How it is that you feel as a competitive golfer knowing that you're fun loving and that you can still compete at a competitive level?
What does that feel like to know that about yourself and be there as if you're already in that spot?
I feel very relaxed and calm.
He's feels very relaxed and calm.
Very good.
I feel very confident over the shot.
He feels very confident.
Excellent!
So this is how he focuses on his feelings.
He thinks about his intention and then he puts himself in that place as if he's already there.
And he can actually feel himself being in the place that he already wants to be in.
That's how you focus on your feelings when you're in hypnosis.